You had just finished a year worth 30
million, which is crazy, but it's nothing
compared to today.
And what we did for 4 and a half.
You still see yourself a lot on Wiad Total.  The
first goal is a billion in
turnover, which for us means 1
million euros per year.  VOD which is the
big thing we can do today in the
group, it's 90% of my time, there's an
all-encompassing vo.  [music] There
are no great results without
great effort.  He is an entrepreneur
because his whole family believes in it.
[music] I feel a very strong
social calling to bring
people [music] into the world who will change
something.
Within the random there was a
small window of secondaries which
according to me is a big taboo in Italy.  I
made a couple of million.
He is Paolo De Nadai, born in 1988 and
founder of WROAD, perhaps the
best-known travel company in Italy.  Here it
raised $58 million in a
round led by Airbnb to expand
into the United States.  News reports
say Airbnb has acquired about 10%
of the company, so if you do the math,
the valuation could be closer to $
400 million to $500 million.  And Paolo, who
still owns a significant stake through his holding company
, could be a hundred
millionaire on paper by the time he's not even 40 years old.  Very different from 2022
when I first met him
.  At that time, Wead had closed the year
with a turnover of almost 30 million,
but it grew year after year, reaching
25 and exceeding 100 million.  In
that interview Paolo told me about
his journey from attending
Zonda school at 18 until the birth of
Wead.